var chapters = [
  { chapter: 1, title: "The need for Innovation" },
  { chapter: 2, title: "Flow of Ideas" },
  { chapter: 3, title: "Everyone is creative" },
  { chapter: 4, title: "Creative Connections Power Tools" },
];

var allQuestionAnswers = [
  {
    question:
      "Who said it?<br />“Every organization, not just business, needs one core competence and that is innovation”.",
    options: [
      "Henri Fayol",
      "F.W.Taylor",
      "Peter F.Drucker",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
    answer: "Peter F.Drucker",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Application of better solutions that meet customer’s new and changed requirements, their implicit needs, or existing market needs is called as:",
    options: ["Improvement", "Invention", "Innovation", "Kaizen"],
    answer: "Innovation",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the definition of innovation?",
    options: [
      "Discovery of a new idea",
      "Profitable implementation of strategic and creative ideas",
      "Creation of the idea or method.",
      "Doing the same thing better",
      "Implementation of a new idea on no-profit-no-loss basis",
    ],
    answer: "Profitable implementation of strategic and creative ideas",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The innovations to the light bulb from incandescent to compact fluorescent (CFL) then LED technologies which offer greater efficiency, durability and brightness are examples of:",
    options: [
      "Efficiency innovation",
      "Evolutionary innovation",
      "Revolutionary innovation",
      "Profitable strategy",
    ],
    answer: "Evolutionary innovation",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The need for innovation is there because we are in the midst of a significant transition, largely because of three main factors:<br />1.\tTechnology<br />2.\tThe world is becoming more accessible<br />Which is the third factor?",
    options: [
      "Employees ever demanding more",
      "Recession",
      "Customers ever demanding more",
      "Inflation",
    ],
    answer: "Customers ever demanding more",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In a survey, some seven hundred organizations worldwide were surveyed, in which 84% of business leaders agreed that innovation is:",
    options: [
      "Not required",
      "More a critical factor than earlier",
      "Expensive and impracticable load",
      "Not contributing to bottom-line",
    ],
    answer: "More a critical factor than earlier",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whenever managers become so accustomed to dealing with existing products and processes that they are complacent and literally blind to new ideas, a disease called -------------------- strikes them.",
    options: [
      "Alzheimer’s",
      "Parkinson’s",
      "Down syndrome",
      "Thomas Lawson Syndrome",
    ],
    answer: "Thomas Lawson Syndrome",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Successful innovators say that ideas that pay off have gone through four steps of development. <br />•\tThe idea is conceived<br />•\tMore people become involved as the idea is ---------------------<br />•\tThe idea is publicized and everyone understands its nature and scope. People investigate its potential, measure its range, and evaluate its economic feasibility<br />•\tThe innovation represented by the idea is adopted and put into practice.",
    options: ["Rejected", "Accepted", "Discussed and examined", "Criticized"],
    answer: "Discussed and examined",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Fill in the blanks:<br />There are four innovation styles:<br />o\tVisioning<br />o\t--------------<br />o\tExperimenting<br />o\tModifying",
    options: ["Commissioning", "Exploring", "Researching", "Observation"],
    answer: "Exploring",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Fill in the blanks:<br />You should think “out of the -----------” when you are alone in your study room, particularly early in the morning, and ask yourself, “what can I do to fulfil the new customer needs? How can I implement a distinctly new idea so that the organization and the customer will get benefitted? How can I come out of the daily rut, and think something different than all the others who are busy in just the routine matters?",
    options: ["World", "Room", "Box", "Head"],
    answer: "Box",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Say true or false:<br />1.\tMost people have their emotional attachment to “the way they did the things around there” and so do not take the leap to a new way. <br />2.\tIt is hard work to stay the course and confront the natural tendency to return to their old and comfortable way of doing this. <br />3.\tIt is hard work to move people away from their sacred traditions and their tendency to conform to industry norms. <br />4.\tIt is easy to get people to admit that what they are doing today might not work anymore.",
    options: [
      "All are true",
      "1 is false, rest are true",
      "2 is false, rest are true",
      "4 is false, rest are true",
    ],
    answer: "4 is false, rest are true",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The company called Zundapp was forced into liquidation in 1984 because:",
    options: [
      "It was a bad company",
      "The company did not control costs",
      "The company remained blind to the changes taking place around it.",
      "There was labor trouble in the company.",
    ],
    answer: "The company remained blind to the changes taking place around it.",
    chapter: 1,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "Who leaped from the bath with the displacement theory?",
    options: ["Einstein", "Archimedes", "Aristotle", "John J. Moran"],
    answer: "Archimedes",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Degree to which one can think of different and more effective approaches is:",
    options: ["Invention", "Improvement", "Creativity", "Intuition"],
    answer: "Creativity",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who said that instead of one mode of thought, each person actually had two modes of thought; one, freely associative, being the idea generator; the other, which worked in a step-by-step logical fashion, acting as a filter?",
    options: [
      "Einstein",
      "Archimedes",
      "Aristotle",
      "Alex Osborn",
      "John J. Moran",
    ],
    answer: "Alex Osborn",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The easiest way to improve your problem sensitivity is to keep in mind that every business operation, every human relation technique, every man-made article can be:",
    options: [
      "Spoiled",
      "Managed",
      "Improved further",
      "Made cheaper to manufacture",
    ],
    answer: "Improved further",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "We must remember that in the beginning, gathering of quantity of ideas is important. We should not mix evaluation of the ideas with gathering the ideas. We should get our ideas first, and worry about whether are good or not later on.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Suppose you get a stray idea, do not depend on memory. You will forget the idea if you depend on memory. So what should you do?",
    options: [
      "Call a meeting",
      "Inform your superiors",
      "Implement it",
      "Immediately write it down",
    ],
    answer: "Immediately write it down",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "You may find that you create best in some special location such as:",
    options: [
      "Cabin, Office, conference room",
      "Living room, kitchen, bedroom",
      "Toilet, balcony, garden",
      "In front of mirror, computer, paintings",
    ],
    answer: "Toilet, balcony, garden",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "To postpone an important task is called as:",
    options: ["Delay", "Laziness", "Inefficiency", "Procrastination"],
    answer: "Procrastination",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Finding new ways to vary existing conditions, finding new ways to adapt existing ideas to new conditions, or creating a new modification of something that will fit in existing condition are the needs of the day and matters connected with:",
    options: ["Originality", "Procrastination", "Invention", "Idea fluency."],
    answer: "Originality",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What is required for not forgetting to be original?",
    options: [
      "Give yourself a quota",
      "Set a deadline",
      "Use of idea checklists",
      "Making notes",
    ],
    answer: "Use of idea checklists",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Being willing to consider a wide variety of approaches to a problem is the quality of:",
    options: [
      "Problem sensitivity",
      "Idea fluency",
      "Creative flexibility",
      "Originality",
    ],
    answer: "Creative flexibility",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "Taking a shower is a simple and effective way to:",
    options: [
      "Impress people",
      "Improve personality",
      "Remove mental block",
      "Improve creativity",
    ],
    answer: "Remove mental block",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A great trick for disarming mental blocks that do not seem to go away is:",
    options: [
      "Change the environment",
      "Change the channel",
      "engage in any high intensity activity or exercise",
      "All the above",
    ],
    answer: "All the above",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Solving problems through an indirect and creative approach, using reasoning that is not immediately obvious and involving ideas that may not be obtainable by using only traditional step-by-step logic is:",
    options: [
      "Change the environment",
      "Change the channel",
      "engage in any high intensity activity or exercise",
      "lateral thinking",
    ],
    answer: "lateral thinking",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Look at the following factors:<br />•\tGiving people more autonomy<br />•\tOpen and honest communication<br />•\tA fun, inspiring meeting room<br />•\tSimplified rules and processes<br />•\tRecognizing that not changing, not trying anything new is often the biggest risk<br />These factors:",
    options: [
      "help creativity flow",
      "block creativity",
      "reduce effectiveness of team work",
      "reduce motivation",
    ],
    answer: "help creativity flow",
    chapter: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Say true or false:<br />1.\tSome individuals have a greater ability to discover new and often amazing ideas than others do.<br />2.\tIf the definition of creativity is "the discovery of a new connec¬tion," then everyone has the ability to be creative.<br />3.\tBill Gates is a creative thinker in the computer field as well as equally creatively inclined with gardening. <br />4.\tGreat creative thinkers have an insatiable appetite for understanding how things work and for connecting new thoughts with old ones.',
    options: [
      "1 is false, rest are true",
      "2 is false, rest are true",
      "3 is false, rest are true",
      "4 is false, rest are true",
    ],
    answer: "3 is false, rest are true",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which side of the brain is supposed to dominate language, logic, and scientific and analytical tasks (more details)?",
    options: ["Left", "Right", "Top", "Bottom"],
    answer: "Left",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which side of the brain is supposed to dominate visual, spa¬tial, and artistic tasks (more abstract processes)?",
    options: ["Left", "Right", "Top", "Bottom"],
    answer: "Right",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who believes that everyone has the capacity to be innovative, and chooses not to measure whether a person is inno¬vative, but instead seeks to understand or discover the unique way in which a person is innovative?",
    options: [
      "Bill Gates",
      "Wayne Gretsky",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "William Miller",
    ],
    answer: "William Miller",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which is the innovation style described below?<br />•\t"Let\'s develop a clear sense of purpose and goals to focus and drive the creative energy."<br />•\tPeople who favor this style trust their instincts and like to make decisions. They seek solutions that focus on maximizing potential rather than focusing on what has gone on in the past.',
    options: ["Visioning", "Exploring", "Experimenting", "Modifying"],
    answer: "Visioning",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which is the innovation style described below?<br />•\t"Let\'s travel around places and find things in new directions and see where we end up."<br />•\tPeople who favor this style like using their insights to guide them. They tend to question assumptions and often will try to implement their ideas despite resistance from others. They are adventurous, dislike routine, and like to be challenged.',
    options: ["Visioning", "Exploring", "Experimenting", "Modifying"],
    answer: "Exploring",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "There are three principles of creative thinking:<br />1.\tBelieve In creativity<br />2.\tBe curious<br />What is the third one?",
    options: [
      "Creativity is an integral part of the DNA",
      "Discover new connections",
      "Stay in your comfort zones",
      "Everyone is creative in the same way",
    ],
    answer: "Discover new connections",
    chapter: 3,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who said it?<br />'Imagination is more important than knowledge.\"",
    options: ["Albert Einstein", "Karl Marx", "Tolstoy", "J.R.D.Tata"],
    answer: "Albert Einstein",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In order to stand out from the crowd, you must be able to see something ------------------------ than what others are seeing and then, of course, you must put this new insight into action",
    options: [
      "In the dark",
      "Distinctly new and better",
      "Far away",
      "Smaller",
    ],
    answer: "Distinctly new and better",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Fill in the blanks:<br />Here are several ways to burn new pathways and strengthen your imagination:<br />1.\tImagine more than one use for your product or service<br />2.\tUse your imagination to -------------of what is expected<br />3.\tLook to other industries or areas for inspiration.\t<br />4.\tImagine the wildest idea you can and then tame this wild idea.",
    options: [
      "Do the opposite",
      "Look to the other side",
      "Jump to the back side",
      "Make proper use",
    ],
    answer: "Do the opposite",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What are stimuli?",
    options: [
      "Use of a product, different than normal",
      "To do opposite of what is expected",
      "Something that encourages activity in people",
      "New and distinctly better idea",
    ],
    answer: "Something that encourages activity in people",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Historical review, Children, List of trends, Television, old files are sources of:",
    options: [
      "Distress",
      "Diverse stimuli",
      "Breaking news",
      "Broader perspective",
    ],
    answer: "Diverse stimuli",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />We have a tendency to trash the past and hold the perception that an idea from five years ago will be of little use in helping to solve our current challenge. However, elements of previous solutions or ideas can prove to be very valuable fuel for jumpstarting our idea engines. Look at ideas such as bell-bottom jeans, disco music, scoot¬ers, pogo sticks, and roller skates, all of which have resurfaced.",
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.10",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.10",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Identify organizations that have achieved excellence in your particular challenge area. <br />?\tFor example, if you are looking for new ideas for "organizing cus¬tomer flow," you might want to investigate what Disney has done to orga¬nize their customer flow so everything runs smoothly at their theme parks or what McDonald\'s has done in order to serve their customers quickly.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.10",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Being obsessed with the challenge requires one to "live and breathe the chal¬lenge." It means interviewing the "experts" and observing actual cus¬tomer behavior. It means learning about the origins of the challenge and investigating it from all angles. Seek out all the information—all the facts, opinions, samples, and reviews you can find on the subject.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.10",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />"Solving cus¬tomer problems sparks innovation." One of the most fertile areas for identifying new ideas is discovering what frustrates others about the cur¬rent product, service, or process. While it is always great to focus on what is wonderful, the team might want to take a quick look at what is not so wonderful.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.10",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Great ideas already exist somewhere else in the universe. All you need to do is find them and adopt them as your own. Find out what others are doing well. Do not limit the stimuli to your own company and only "fast adapt" ideas from within the four walls of your own organization.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 8",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.9",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.6",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 7",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.6",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Creative thinking is a bit like cooking: a little of this and a little of that. Creative thinkers are aware of the objects or ideas around them and look for new connections through combining diverse objects or ideas.",
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 1",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.2",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.5",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 3",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.5",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />When you are faced with a creative challenge, a good technique is to think of other chal¬lenges that might be similar. <br />For example, find similarities in nature: How is the organization like a tree, or how is the process like a tornado?",
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 4",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.3",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.2",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 1",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No. 4",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Sometimes the problem or situation is overwhelming in its complexity. A good tech¬nique in this case is to break the problem down bit by bit so that the focus is on the "bits" instead of on the whole problem all at once. It is then eas¬ier to understand what is driving the problem and identify unique ideas to solve part, if not all, of the problem. Pulling apart a product or service to find the underlying "DNA" elements is easy.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 4",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.5",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.3",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 2",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.3",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which creative connections Power tool is described below?<br />Once the steps in the process or attributes of the product or service have been "listed," they can be "twisted" to find new ideas.',
    options: [
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 6",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.4",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No.2",
      "Creative connections Power Tool No. 3",
    ],
    answer: "Creative connections Power Tool No.2",
    chapter: 4,
    isAnswered: false,
    isFlagged: false,
    marks: 1,
    selectedAnswer: "",
  },
];
